passnownow.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy | Passnownow

**Our Commitment to Privacy**  
PassNowNow knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy.  
This policy will answer the following questions:

  * What personally identifiable information does PassNowNow collect from me?
  * What are cookies and how does PassNowNow use them?
  * How does PassNowNow use my information?
  * Who is collecting information?
  * With whom does PassNowNow share my information?
  * What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?
  * What is PassNowNow’s policy on allowing me to update, correct, or delete my personally identifiable information?
  * What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?
  * How does PassNowNow protect children’s privacy?
  * What else should I know about my privacy?

**What personally identifiable information does PassNowNow collect from me?**  
PassNowNow collects information in several ways from different parts of our services.  
Some personal information is gathered when you register. PassNowNow may ask for your name, e-mail address, and/or additional information. We may also ask you to choose a username and password.  
In addition to the information we collect when you register, we may ask you for personal information at other times, such as when you contact our technical support team. Furthermore, when you send e-mail, user surveys, or other communication to PassNowNow, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests, and improve our services.

**What are cookies and how does PassNowNow use them?**  
As part of our offering and providing customizable and personalized services, PassNowNow uses cookies to temporarily store information about you. A cookie is a small file on your own computer containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to better display our website, to save you time, to provide better technical support, for advertising purposes, and to anonymously track website usage. For example, cookies help us to:

  1. Keep track of whether you are signed in or have previously signed in so that we can display all the features that are available to you.
  2. Remember your settings on the pages you visit, so that we can display your preferred content the next time you visit.
  3. Know your username when you submit a technical support request so that you don’t have to type it in.
  4. Advertise to potential customers on other websites around the web.
  5. Anonymously track website usage in the aggregate to help improve our services.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features and services (particularly those that require you to sign in) may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

**How does PassNowNow use my information?**  
PassNowNow’s goals in collecting personal information are to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our site and a high level of technical support.  
PassNowNow does research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us upon registration, from our server log files, or from surveys. We do this to better understand and serve our users; for instance, this information often gives us ideas for improving our services. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis.

**Who is collecting information?**  
When you are on the PassNowNow site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with PassNowNow alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected or maintained by any company other than PassNowNow, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer.

**With whom does PassNowNow share my information?**  
As a general rule, PassNowNow will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. The following describes some of the reasons that your information may be disclosed.  
Business Partners & Sponsors – PassNowNow will never disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors, unless it is specifically described to you prior to data collection or prior to transferring the data. If personally identifying data about you will be shared, we will tell you before we collect or transfer the data. If PassNowNow becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
Third Party Data & Data in the Aggregate – Under confidentiality agreements, PassNowNow may match user information with third party data. Also, PassNowNow discloses aggregated user statistics (for example, 22% of our users are from South West Nigeria) in order to describe our services to current and prospective partners and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.  
Other –  PassNowNow may release personal information if it has a good faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request; (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property, or safety of PassNowNow, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law.

**What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?**  
PassNowNow may from time to time, send you e-mail regarding our services and activities. Only PassNowNow will send you these direct mailings. You can choose not to receive these e-mails by clicking the unsubscribe link in any e-mail or contacting help@passnownow.com.  
You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies.  
PassNowNow does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service.

**What is PassNowNow’s policy on allowing me to update, correct or delete my personally identifiable information?**  
You may edit your account information at any time by logging into your account and clicking the Account or Profile link. We recommend that you review your personal information periodically to ensure that it is accurate, complete, and current.  
If you have forgotten your password, go to the password request form. A new password will be sent to the e-mail address you specified during registration. For all other problems logging into PassNowNow services, please contact technical support for that service.  
Please contact technical support for further instructions about deleting or deactivating your account for any PassNowNow service. Residual information will remain within our archive records.

**What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?**  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.  
Your registered accounts are password-protected so that you and only you have access to any personal information you have entered in your account. You may edit your account information at any time by logging into your account and clicking the Account or Profile link.  
For your protection, remember to log out of all accounts before closing your browser. There is a log out link available on most PassNowNow pages. After logging out, make sure to close all browser windows. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information if you share a computer with someone else or are using a public computer.  
We restrict access to personal information to PassNowNow employees, suppliers, and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop, or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

**How does PassNowNow protect children’s privacy?**  
PassNowNow does not ask a child under 11 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity.

**What else should I know about my privacy?**  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online (for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas) that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.  
Some PassNowNow services offer the option to show your name and e-mail address in various capacities. If you decide to show your name and e-mail address, you are making it available to others over the Internet. (In particular, if you have chosen to have your name displayed on your activity pages. Please do not include any information on your profile that you do not want to disclose over the Internet.

**Additional Information**  
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat your personal information by placing a prominent notice on our websites.  
If you have a question regarding this statement, or if a question was not addressed in this privacy policy, you may contact technical support athelp@passnownow.com. We will do our best to answer your question/s promptly and accurately.
